VRAJ PATEL

Edmonton, AB | 0810vrajpatel@gmail.com | 825-886-8101

INTRODUCTION

Dedicated and customer-focused store associate with experience in providing excellent customer service and maintaining a neat and organized retail environment. Aiming to contribute strong communication and organizational skills to a dynamic retail team. have over 2 years of experience.

EXPERIENCE

Big Bazaar (Anand, Gujarat, India)

Jan 2023 - Nov 2023

Part Time: Cashier/POS

- Registers sales on a **cash/POS register** by scanning items, itemizing and totaling customers purchases.
- Stocking, promptly unloads trucks and deliveries.
- Customer Services including handling questions and concerns
- Binning overstock merchandise.
- Helped management and customers as needed.
- Accommodated customers with the written of their unwanted items.
- Assisted customers with locating items.

D-Mart (Anand, Gujarat, India)

Mar 2022 - Dec 2022

Role: Customer Service Representative

- Resolve customer complaints via phone, email, mail or social media.
- Use telephones to reach out to customers.
- Greet customers warmly and ascertain problem or reason for calling.
- Assist with placement of orders, refunds or exchanges.

SKILLS

- Superb verbal, written, and interpersonal abilities
- Solid mathematical abilities
- Word, Excel, and PowerPoint for documentation purposes
- Decent both as an individual contributor and a team player
- Thrive in a multicultural team setting
- Effectively managing one's time.
- Operating in a high-pressure environment.

- Problem solving.
- Initiative.

EDUCATION

PGDip - Full Stack Web-Development & Professional Communication

Present

• MacEwan University (Edmonton, AB)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

June 2020 - May 2023

• Charotar University of Science and Technology (CHARUSAT) (Changa, GJ, India)

AVAILIBILITY

• Day and Night Both

Sunday	Monday	Tuesday	Wednesday	Thursday	Friday	Saturday
Open	Open	Open	Open	Open	Open	Open